Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
What's going on. Hop?
You back again?
Oh. sick!
Find good one?
Yeah. Ten Tigers of Kwangtung.
This is gold.
Bride With White Hair.
Chinese. no subtitles.
Hey. Hop. do you have
any early Shaw Brothers?
There's a guy
who does Leopard style...
Leopard style. Dragon style...
fly through air. fight on water.
Crouching Tiger.
Spanking Monkey.
I know you.
Another white boy
who wants to know kung-fu.
Kick the ass.
Get the girls.
Only storage back here.
Where did you get this?
It was here...
when my grandfather
opened this shop...
hundred years ago.
He waited for a man
to come to pick it up...
return to rightful owner.
Man never came.
My father take over the shop.
Waited. too. Long time.
Now me.
That's a Northern Temple-style
bo staff.
Same kind the thirteen monks used
to save the Tang Emperor.
I've seen it before.
That exact one.
I've had dreams about it.
You know why?
You watch
too much Hong Kong Phooey.
Come.
Come on.
I give you
five awesome Bruce Lee movie...
for very sick price.
You're the man. Hop.
Jason!
Hey. What's up?
Not much.
Just. you know. cruisin'.
You been down to Chinatown.
What's up with that?
Kung-fu.
Are you serious?
I'm not supposed
to talk about it...
not under the kung-fu code.
Hey. look. The new kid's
makin' time with the hoodsies.
J-boy. you still riding
this loser cruiser?
You need to get a motor
for this shit.
What we got here?
Just some bootlegs. no big deal.
"Enter the Dragon"?
"The Bride With White Hair"?
Yeah. that's actually very good.
Come on. let him go.
Yeah. don't. He knows kung-fu.
What?
You think you're Chinese?
You hangin' out
with them Chinks in C-town?
What's up with you?
Let's see some. man.
Come on.
Let's see some kung-fu. huh?
Kung-fu master.
Want some tae kwon do. huh?
Yo. Lupo.
He's hangin' out with that
old Chink cashes checks.
You in tight with the old man?
Just shut up and do it!
It's late. man.
He's probably gone home.
He's not here. Let's just go.
Who's there?
Kung-fu boy.
You back
for more good-price movie?
I told you.
best deal in Chinatown.
Come in.
Want some tea?
Red Sox game is on.
Yankees winning. Very bad.
Who's with you?
Friend?
Where you keep the cash?
I said.
where do you keep the cash?
- Please...
- Come on. old man!
Stay here!
Found your Xbox.
Hop!
Jesus. Lupo!
- What the hell. man?
- You shot him!
Take it.
Must return to rightful owner.
Run.
You didn't see that. yo.
You didn't see that!
Come here. you little shit!
Lupo. come on. man! Just don't...
- You didn't see nothing!
- Calm down. Lupo.
Hey. chill. man. Come on.
- Put the gun down.
- Shut up!
Maybe I pulled the trigger.
but we're all in this together!
But this little cockroach.
he ain't one of us!
Excuse me.
I don't know where I am.
I don't know how I got here.
I remember falling.
What? This?
You want this?
I don't know what you're saying.
I can't understand you!
That's because
you're not listening!
Behind you!
I don't know where I am...
or how I got here...
and who those guys were
that wanted to kill me.
But whatever you did back there
was sick.
No. Drunken Fist.
Secret kung-fu of the South.
I'm Lu Yan. traveling scholar.
What land do you come from. monk?
I'm not a monk.
I'm Jason.
Jason Tripitikas.
from South Boston.
Is this a dream?
No.
Where you came from
is the dream...
through the Gate of No Gate.
Is that like a wormhole
or something?
No. It means
you are either a Zen master...
or you carry something
very special.
This?
It was in a pawn shop. waiting
for a man to pick it up...
and return it
to its rightful owner.
What?
It's long been foretold...
that a seeker will come...
to return the staff and end
the reign of the Jade Warlord.
Return the staff to who?
The Monkey King.
Born of a stone...
on the mountain of fruit
and flowers.
With his weapon in hand.
his chi became like fire...
his stick fighting like magic.
He defied the order
of the land...
but the Jade Army
could not defeat him.
The Monkey King crushed
every soldier sent to stop him.
With his magical staff.
he was unbeatable.
Word of his disobedience...
traveled deep
within the Forbidden Kingdom...
to the Five Elements Mountain.
land of the immortals.
Once every 500 years...
the Jade Emperor hosts
the Peach Banquet.
It is here.
the heavenly ministers gather...
to celebrate their longevity...
and drink
the elixir of immortality.
One sip of this heavenly brew
will give everlasting life...
free from mortal suffering
and desire.
Into the banquet. the
Monkey King crashed. uninvited.
The Jade Emperor was
enchanted by the Monkey King.
But the Jade Warlord
was not amused.
As master of the army...
the Warlord demanded
the Monkey King bow down to him.
He's a bit unrefined.
that's all.
Give the naughty monkey
a title and let him go.
Satisfied all was well
in heaven and earth...
the supremely high Emperor...
left to begin
his 500 years meditation...
leaving the Jade Warlord
in charge by mandate of heaven.
But rather than obey
the Jade Emperor's command...
the Warlord challenged
the Monkey King to a duel.
High atop Five Elements Mountain
in the Warlord's palace...
the battle of immortals
was fought...
to prove once and for all
whose skills were supreme.
Most excellent stick fighting.
Sun Wukong.
But without your weapon. you're
nothing but a lowly hermit!
No more weapons.
no more chi magic.
Fist against fist.
The Monkey King
was too trusting...
and believed
the Warlord's words...
laying down his magic weapon.
Realizing he'd been tricked. the
Monkey King cast the staff...
out into the Middle Kingdom.
Martial art
is based on deception...
my friend.
Being immortal. the Monkey King
could not be killed...
only trapped in stone...
where he waits for the seeker
from the prophesy...
to return to him his great weapon
and finally free him.
That's what I heard. anyway.
Long time ago.
How long has he been imprisoned?
Five hundred years.
give or take a few decades.
They say
when the Monkey King is free...
the Jade Emperor will return.
How do I get home?
You must return the staff
to Five Elements Mountain.
You must free the Monkey King.
I can't free the Monkey King.
I gotta get home.
Innkeeper! More wine.
Jeez. don't you think
you've had one too many?
Wine is my inspiration.
In some parts.
I am known as the Poet.
Gambei.
In other parts.
I am known as the Beggar.
What do we do now?
How good is your kung-fu?
He who speaks does not know.
He who knows does not speak.
Surely. you are masterful.
Where did you get that weapon?
It's a fake.
You can find anything these days
on the Silk Road.
Out of way. old fool.
Hand it over.
Hand over the weapon... or die.
Go!
Lu. help!
Protect yourself!
What?
Let's go!
Where are you going?
- Jump!
- I don't think so!
Don't think! Just do!
Come on!
Thank you!
Such skills. child!
Are you
from northern mountains?
She is Golden Sparrow.
from the south.
You really saved
our lives back there.
I don't know
what we would have done...
if you hadn't come along.
She does not think The Drunken
Immortal needed his life saved.
You're immortal?
What do you run from. child?
Bounty hunters
trying to stop her...
from reaching
the Five Elements Mountain.
I suggest
you keep riding west...
and only stop
to water your horses.
You're not coming?
The journey
to Five Elements Mountain...
crosses barrens and deserts.
Unspeakable dangers.
Worst of all. no wine.
His elixir.
Every immortal has one.
I'm very sorry.
Without wine. I would perish.
You must understand this.
No. You must understand this.
This is insane!
- You wish to get home?
- Yes.
Then listen well!
If you die here...
you'll be found dead
in the world you left behind.
Do you understand?
My jug is getting low.
I must say goodbye. Bye-bye.
Lu.
Wait!
Let him go.
You are the one
to return the staff. not him.
How good is your kung-fu?
He's got no kung-fu.
None!
Lu. wait!
Teach me.
Teach me to fight!
Swing soft. cut hard!
At the same time!
He's terrible.
I've been your weed-whacker
for two days now...
while you sit on your horse
like the King of England.
When are you gonna
teach me kung-fu?
- You want to learn kung-fu?
- Yeah.
I teach you kung-fu.
That's called strike.
Tomorrow. I'll teach you block.
Let's go.
Swing soft. cut hard.
You think you'll teach me
the No Shadow Kick?
And the Buddha Palm Technique?
There's a guy
in Virtual Fighter 2...
that does
the Buddha Palm technique.
Thanks. Lu.
And he does the...
the Iron Elbow...
and he does
the One-Fingered Death Touch.
The cup's full.
Stop! It's full.
Exactly.
How can you fill your cup
if already full?
How can you learn kung-fu?
You already know so much.
No Shadow Kick. Buddha Palm!
Empty your cup.
Hopeless.
It is hopeless.
It is said that music...
is a bridge
between earth and heaven.
It's beautiful.
It belonged to her mother.
Lu Yan?
Sparrow!
Are you all right?
Jason. what happened?
He took it! The staff!
The Jade Warlord
has sent a bounty hunter.
We are doomed.
That's his horse.
He must be inside.
Why would he take refuge
in a temple?
That's what I intend
to find out.
Wait with the horses.
Good to get off my feet.
Long day.
So. where are you from?
Shandong Province?
You look like
the Shandong Province type.
You come here often?
That staff
doesn't belong to you.
You have to give it to me.
or somebody might get hurt.
What kind of monk are you?
Stealing from travelers.
A silent one. I see.
Or deaf.
I'm speaking to you. monk!
Praying Mantis.
Very good...
for catching bugs.
But not tiger!
You tried to steal the staff
for the Warlord!
No. fool!
I'm on a mission to find
the seeker of the staff.
You found him.
How long have you been searching
for the staff?
As long as I can remember.
Jason. go deeper!
Must taste bitter before sweet.
Horse stance. Grow roots.
Horse stance.
Very good... for taking a dump.
Enough from you!
He's my student. not yours!
Two tigers cannot live
on the same mountain.
Two masters cannot teach
the same student!
If he is really to learn
the kung-fu...
he must develop speed.
accuracy. and power.
Hey! I know that.
It's the Way
of the Intercepting Fist.
Bruce Lee?
I will punch.
You block.
Ready?
What did I teach you
about the Snake?
Now you punch me.
See?
Again. You punch him again.
Snake!
He's not ready for Snake.
Perhaps Eagle.
Crane! Crane!
Stop!
I've had enough!
No more!
No more silent riddles!
And no more empty cups!
First. you show respect
to your teachers!
So. what about the two tigers
on one mountain?
We can kill each other
when it's over.
Kung-fu.
Hard work over time
to accomplish skill.
A painter can hace kung-fu.
Or the butcher who cuts meat
every day with such skill...
his knife never touches bone.
Learn the form.
but seek the formless.
Hear the soundless.
Learn it all.
then forget it all.
Learn The Way.
then find your own way.
The musician can hace kung-fu...
or the poet who paints pictures
with words...
and makes emperors weep.
This. too. is kung-fu.
But do not name it. my friend.
for it is like water.
Nothing is softer than water...
yet it can overcome rock.
It does not fight.
It flows around the opponent.
Formless. nameless...
the true master dwells within.
Only you can free him.
Behold the tyranny
of the Warlord.
He must be stopped.
He must be killed for his crimes
and his head put on a post.
But we must not feel hatred
towards him. or he wins.
If he speaks of compassion
for this devil...
he should go back to his temple
and pray.
Our mission is not one of peace.
Go back
to your mother and father.
You are but a child.
They are dead.
And she's not a child.
Not anymore.
Her father...
was a government official
who opposed the Warlord.
And so. to set an example...
the Warlord dispatched
his troops into the night.
Legion upon legion poured out
of the Five Elements Mountain...
into the lowlands
of the Middle Kingdom.
Screams of innocent people
hung in the night air.
When it was over. charred ruins
were all that remained.
That. and a lonely child. hidden
in the well by her mother...
ruthlessly murdered
by an arrow...
from the Warlord's bow.
When she reaches
the Warlord's palace...
she will
not offer him forgiveness...
monk.
She will offer him...
this...
a jade dart...
that can kill an immortal.
Long has she practiced.
Vengeance has a way
of rebounding upon oneself.
Master of sensitivity.
Damn.
This desert is hot.
This is not a desert.
That is the desert!
I hope you know
where you're going!
Crazy monk.
A monk on a mission.
And where does he lead us?
Across a desert to nowhere.
We're not going to make it.
are we?
And even if we do. we still
have to face the Jade Army.
What if I can't handle it?
What if I freeze?
Don't forget to breathe.
If we don't find water soon.
we will perish.
Perhaps a Taoist immortal
can make rain.
If he truly is
a Taoist immortal.
You are an insult
to the name of Buddha!
Blasphemy!
Look!
I lead you to the mountain!
Out there!
Can you see them...
in the clouds?
A two-headed lion.
Right there.
See?
Yeah. I see.
See that one?
Right there.
coming up behind it?
Like a wave?
Looks like the Green Monster.
Green monster?
You mean dragon.
No. I mean Fenway Park.
They call the left field fence
the Green Monster.
It's true.
It does kind of look like
a dragon. though. doesn't it?
Have you family
back in this land you come from?
My mother.
Father?
Never knew him.
Do you ever long for him?
Wonder who he was?
Maybe the only thing
I've ever been good at...
pretending that I don't.
She is sorry.
How romantic.
Men will tell you
what you want to hear. Sparrow.
But in the end. they will
leave you with nothing.
You survived the River of Sand.
Impressive.
And you. boy...
so far from home.
I can ensure your safe return.
Just bring the weapon forward.
I don't think so.
Why do you want the staff?
When I deliver
the lost weapon...
the Jade Warlord shall grant me
the Elixir of Immortality.
An orphan girl.
a lost traveler...
an old drunk.
and a monk who has failed...
at the same task
for half his life.
Misfits following a misfit
in hopes of rescuing... a misfit.
Kill them.
Lu! You okay?
Just thirsty.
It's okay. He's immortal. right?
I mean. he is. right?
Wine. He needs his wine!
There is nothing we can do.
What are you saying?
We have to do something!
I'm afraid the wound
is too deep.
He will not survive it.
He needs wine.
He's one of the Eight Immortals.
Wine is his elixir. Please.
We will send a walking monk.
Don't you have a running monk?
When I was your age...
I was a scholar-warrior
in training.
My arrow was good.
So. too. my kung-fu.
So I was chosen to take
the civil examinations.
To pass would place me...
in the very short line
of scholar immortals.
I failed.
You're not an immortal?
If one
does not attach himself...
to people and desires...
never shall his heart be broken.
But then...
does he ever truly live?
I would rather die a mortal...
who has cared about someone...
than a man free...
from his own death.
I don't want to lose you.
Forget about me.
There is only one
Elixir of Immortality.
It is
the Emperor's mix of jade...
cinnabar. and salts of mercury.
It is forever stored in
the realm of the Jade Palace...
high in the Jade Firmament.
rarely touched by mortals.
To reach it.
one must take the north road...
and cross the border
of heaven and earth...
only to face the Jade Army.
I'm sorry.
There is no other way.
Yes. there is.
In two nights.
there should be no moon.
We can take the south side
of the fourth peak...
under cover of darkness.
- We have to go now.
- No!
But he's going to die!
We go now. we all die.
There is more at stake.
an entire kingdom.
Your passage home.
We will advance in two nights.
when the moon has ceased.
So be it!
When she met you...
long ago in a tea house...
you were a lost boy
and frightened.
Not the kind
she would stand and fight with.
You've made
a most excellent judgment.
The seeker from the prophecy.
Not quite what I expected.
A man is dying
back on Song Mountain.
I need the Elixir.
And why should I give it to you?
Because I brought you the staff.
The life of your friend
for the power to rule a kingdom?
A most reasonable offer.
This man. a good friend?
And a good teacher.
The man who honors his teacher
honors himself.
However. there is a bit
of a problem with your request.
You see...
I've promised the Elixir
to someone else.
But she
didn't bring you the staff.
I did.
The boy has a point.
My Liege. you made a promise.
There is but one way
to resolve such matters.
A martial challenge...
to the death.
With pleasure.
The Elixir of Immortality.
The prize goes to the winner.
Enough!
The seeker from the prophecy.
I find that quite amusing.
Did you really think. even for
a minute. you stood a chance?
I didn't think so.
She will kill you. witch!
Not if I kill you first.
orphan bitch!
Gambei!
Remember what I taught you!
The statue!
Use the staff!
My turn!
My Lord.
Who are you?
The youngest daughter
of a family you murdered.
Come drink with me.
No!
Sparrow!
Come on.
You're going to be okay.
Jade Warlord?
He's dead.
I thank you.
Is there anything you can do?
Her destiny was written
by her own hand.
I am sorry.
Traveler...
you have come far.
through the Gate of No Gate...
to fulfill the prophecy
of the mortals.
What do you desire. please?
I just want to go home.
Very well.
It is said master and student...
walk the path side-by-side.
They share their destiny until
their paths go separate ways.
I'll never forget you.
I guess that's what being
immortal truly means.
You freed me. traveler.
Now go free yourself.
So what's it gonna be?
You gonna shut up?
Listen. pissant!
I ain't gonna ask you again!
Come on. maggot. get up!
Come on!
You want some more?
Come on.
We don't have to do this.
Take it easy. sir.
You're gonna be fine.
Hop! Hop!
How's he doin'?
It missed his heart.
He'll live.
Of course I'll live.
I'm immortal.
Did you return the staff
to rightful owner?
I did.
You're the man.
Is he gonna be all right?
Looks like it.
I saw what happened.
I work across the street.
You were very brave.
See ya.
Absolutely.
And so the legend is told...
that the Monkey King
began his journey west...
in search of truth...
while the traveler
returned to his world...
to walk the path of the warrior
and find his own truth.
As one tale ends...
so another
begins.
Subtitles by LeapinLar
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm